我知道你现在并不爱我
I know you don't love me now.
错把可爱当恋爱是非常危险的
lt's a dangerous thing to confuse children with angels.
知道共有的元素是什么吗?
Wanna know the common element for the entire group, like he asked?
我来告诉你们 我知道
I'll tell you the answer, because I had that one.
我会回答这个问题
I had that question.
碳 是碳
Uh, carbon. Carbon.
在铅笔芯中 它是以石墨形式存在的
ln pencil lead, it's in the form of graphite...
在煤矿中 它和各种杂质混杂在一起
...in coal, it's mixed up with other impurities...
而在钻石中 它以最坚固的形式存在
...and in the diamond, it's in hard form.
好吧 我们只是需要元素的名字就好
Well, all we really wanted to know was the common element, Donnie...
谢谢你告诉我们这么多不必要的知识
...but thank you for all that unnecessary knowledge. Ha, ha.